[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Guys, you should be working on your bridge assignments.
伙计们，你们应该在做你们的桥梁作业。
We are. We're de-fudging the sticks.
我们正在做。我们在解开那些棍子。
Oh! Shh.
哦！嘘。
Judge Junior's coming back on with his ruling.
法官Junior带着他的裁决回来了。
And his clever word play.
还有他的巧妙文字游戏。
- In the case of the careless cat-sitter,
关于粗心的猫咪看护人一案，
I have reached a verdict.
我已经做出了判决。
Or I should I say purr-dict.
或者我应该说是猫语判决。
Purr-dict? He's pun-believable.
猫语判决？他的双关语真是难以置信。
- Guilty! Case closed.
- 有罪！案件结束。
All right. Break's over.
好了，休息结束。
Time to buckle down and get back to work.
是时候认真工作了。
- Oh. - Yeah.
- 哦。- 是啊。
- Let's do it.
- 我们开始吧。
Did you guys just eat an entire box of fudge pops?
你们刚吃了一整盒巧克力棒吗？
No.
没有。
We ate six boxes.
我们吃了六盒。
[gasps]
[倒吸一口气]
- Okay, this is out of control.
- 好吧，这太过分了。
You kids are eating way too much junk food.
你们这些孩子吃太多垃圾食品了。
- Your mother's right.
你妈妈说得对。
The Harper house is now a healthy house.
哈珀家现在要变成健康之家了。
Only nutritious snacks from here on out.
从现在开始只吃有营养的零食。
[all] Oh!
哦！
Right, Tom?
对吧，汤姆？
- Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
Normally, I'd say you're setting a bad example,
通常我会说你在树立坏榜样，
but the brain freeze you're about to have
但你即将感受到的脑冻结
will say it for me.
会替我说出来的。
Ha!
哈！
[yelps]
[惊叫]
- See, kids?
- 看到了吗，孩子们？
You can't hurt yourself with fruit.
水果是不会伤到你的。
Oh!
噢！
I just bit my tongue.
我刚刚咬到舌头了。
[all] Oh.
[所有人] 哦。
- What happened to the sticks with jokes on them?
- 那些带有笑话的棍子去哪儿了？
I want my bridge to make people laugh.
我希望我的桥能让人发笑。
Oh, I think you've got that covered.
哦，我觉得你已经做到了。
Wait. Is that one of my joke sticks?
等等，那是我的笑话棍吗？
Well, I don't see your name on it.
嗯，上面又没写你名字。
Unless your name is "Where can you find a nosy hot pepper?
除非你的名字叫'哪里能找到爱管闲事的辣椒？'
"Jalapeno business."
'jalapeno business.'（注：英文中jalapeno为辣椒的一种，此处为双关语）
Just give it.
快还给我。
- No! - Oh!
- 不给！- 哦！
[gasps]
（惊呼）
- My bridge. - Whoops.
- 我的桥。- 哎呀。
You did that on purpose!
你是故意的！
No, I didn't. It was an accident.
不，我不是。是个意外。
- Was not. - Was too!
- 不是。 - 就是！
- Not! - Too!
- 不是！ - 就是！
[both] Mom!
[两人] 妈妈！
No, Mom is dealing with Dad's brain freeze.
不，妈妈正在处理爸爸的脑冻结。
[Tom] It hurts so much, Anne.
[汤姆] 这太疼了，安妮。
Too bad we can't go on Judge Junior to settle this.
可惜我们不能上《小法官》来解决这个问题。
We don't need Judge Junior.
我们不需要小法官。
We can take this to a different court.
我们可以把这个带到另一个法庭。
All rise.
全体起立。
Quad Court is now in session.
四重法庭现在开庭。
The Honorable Dawn Harper presiding.
尊敬的Dawn Harper主持。
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿，嘿，嘿。
No fair.
这不公平。
The Honorable Ricky Harper was powdering his wig.
尊敬的Ricky Harper正在扑粉他的假发。
I should be the judge.
我应该当法官。
- Should not. - Should too.
不应该。
- Not! - Too!
应该。
- I'm the better judge. - No, I am.
不应该！
[both shouting]
应该！
Couldn't you both be judges?
你们两个不能都当法官吗？
[grumbles]
[咕哝]
- Sure. - That'll work.
- 当然。 - 那行得通。
Huh. Jalapeno business.
哼。哈拉佩尼奥的生意。
Now I get it!
现在我明白了！
Good one, stick.
好样的，棍子。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na, hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐，嘿！ ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling melody]
[吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping]
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na, hey! ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
[upbeat music]
All right.
好的。
Quad Court's in session.
四方法庭开庭了。
Fine.
好的。
- That felt good. - I know, right?
- 感觉不错。 - 我知道，对吧？
Nicky, can you please tell the court,
尼基，请你告诉法庭，
in your own words, what happened?
用你自己的话，发生了什么？
I was building my bridge, minding my own business,
我正在建我的桥，忙自己的事，
when Colonel Cool Hair came over-- - Objection!
当酷发上校过来时—— - 反对！
My hair is not cool.
我的头发不酷。
It's awesome.
它很棒。
Case closed.
案子结了。
It's not closed.
还没结。
You broke my bridge because I insulted yours.
你毁了我的桥，因为我侮辱了你的。
I swear, Your Honors.
我发誓，尊敬的法官们。
I only broke his bridge because I wanted the joke sticks.
我只是因为想要那些笑话棒才毁了他的桥。
[both gasp]
[两人同时吸气]
So you did do it on purpose.
所以你是故意这么做的。
Fine. I confess.
好吧。我承认。
But I ask the court, is that really what this is all about?
但我请求法庭，这真的就是全部吗？
That's all this is about.
这就是全部。
Dicky Harper, in "The Case of Nicky's Bridge is ♪ Falling Down,
迪基·哈珀，在《尼基的桥在 ♪ 倒下，♪ 倒下，♪ 倒下》中
Falling Down, Falling Down ♪", you are guilty.
♪ 倒下，倒下，倒下 ♪，你有罪。
Dicky Harper, you are hereby sentenced
迪基·哈珀，你因此被判
to carry Nicky Harper's backpack around for one day.
携带尼基·哈珀的书包一整天。
That seems fair.
这看起来很公平。
This... is...
这...真是...
so not fair.
太不公平了。
It seems fair to me.
我觉得挺公平的。
Ooh, a penny.
哦，一枚硬币。
Let's save this little fella for later.
我们留着这个小家伙以后用。
Oh!
哦！
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
I object.
我反对。
[both] We'll allow it.
我们允许。
[upbeat music]
轻快的音乐
Plain yogurt?
原味酸奶？
Delicious ice cream.
美味的冰淇淋。
[chuckles]
（轻笑）
Mm.
嗯。
[gasps]
（吸气声）
I love plain yogurt!
我喜欢原味酸奶！
What a run.
真是一场奔跑。
Now that all that sugar's out of my body,
现在糖分从我体内消失了，
I feel so alive and full of energy.
我感觉充满活力，精力充沛。
Yeah, sugar-free's the way to be.
是的，无糖才是王道。
I feel like I could run another ten miles.
我觉得我可以再跑十英里。
Oh, I could run 11.
哦，我能跑十一英里。
Great, let's go.
太好了，我们走吧。
- Now? - Yeah.
- 现在就去？- 对。
I have to finish my yogurt, so--
我得吃完我的酸奶，所以--
Here, let me help you.
- 来，我帮你。- 不不，我自己来。
- No, no, I got it. - Okay, great, let's go.
- 好的，那我们走吧。
[yelps]
[惊叫]
[Anne] Tom?
安妮？ 汤姆？
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
I love running!
我喜欢跑步！
[yips]
[吠叫]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[all] Ugh.
[所有人] 呃。
Okay.
好吧。
Everyone just close your eyes and imagine
大家闭上眼睛，想象一下
the vegetables are a pizza, the salad is nachos,
蔬菜是披萨，沙拉是玉米片，
and this apple is a fried mac and cheese ball.
而这个苹果是炸芝士通心粉球。
It's working. I can smell the nachos.
起作用了。我能闻到玉米片的味道。
I can smell the mac and cheese.
我能闻到芝士通心粉的味道。
Dawn!
Dawn！
Sorry, Mae.
对不起，Mae。
All we're eating now are fruits and vegetables.
我们现在吃的全是水果和蔬菜。
Our mom is trying to make us eat healthier.
我们的妈妈想让我们吃得更健康。
Mine, too.
我也是。
Luckily my dad packed my lunch this morning.
幸好我爸爸今天早上给我打包了午餐。
Mmm.
嗯。
I love you, Daddy.
爸爸，我爱你。
If anybody asks, I've been here the whole time.
如果有人问起，我一直在这里。
Who's gonna ask?
谁会问呢？
I know it was one of you who toilet papered my tortoise.
我知道是你们中的一个把卫生纸缠在我的乌龟上的。
And when I find out who did this to Shelly,
当我找出是谁对雪莉做了这种事，
you will be sent to the principal's office.
你会被送到校长办公室。
Which is my office.
那其实就是我的办公室。
You will be sent to me.
你会被送到我这里来。
[sighs]
（叹气）
I'm guessing it was Mack.
我猜是麦克的。
Oh, please. I know Mack.
哦，拜托。我了解Mack。
Mack would never do something like that.
Mack绝不会做那种事。
I did it.
是我做的。
I don't know what got into me, but...
我不知道自己怎么了，但是...
it felt great.
感觉很棒。
Now, if you'll excuse me,
现在，如果你们不介意，
I'm going to go burp into the PA system.
我要去对着公共广播系统打嗝。
Huh. You think you know somebody.
哼。你以为你了解某个人。
I'd like to know that cinnamon roll.
我想了解那个肉桂卷。
Mae, look what you did to my shirt.
Mae，看看你对我衬衫做了什么。
Me? I've been sitting here.
我？我一直坐在这里。
No, you borrowed it last week and gave it back with a stain.
不，你上周借了它，还回来时上面有污渍。
- Did not. - Did too.
- 没有。 - 有。
You owe me a new shirt.
你欠我一件新衬衫。
- Do not! - Do too!
- 不欠！ - 欠！
Too bad you guys can't settle this in Quad Court.
可惜你们不能在Quad Court解决这个问题。
Quad Court?
Quad Court？
Yeah, it's like Judge Junior.
是的，就像是小法官。
But with us.
但由我们来裁决。
That's a great idea.
那是个好主意。
We should bring our case to you.
我们应该把我们的案子交给你。
Totally.
完全同意。
I don't really know. It's more of a...
我不太确定。这更像是一个...
family thing.
家庭事务。
Would you guys settle our case in Quad Court
如果我们带零食来，你们会在Quad Court解决我们的案子吗？
if we brought snacks?
你知道，那种我爸爸做的零食？
You know, the kind my daddy makes?
我们会法庭见。
[both] We'll see you in court.
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Quad Court is now in session.
Quad Court现在开庭。
The Honorable Nicky...
尊敬的尼基...
- Ricky... - Dicky...
- 里基... - 迪基...
And Dawn Harper presiding.
和道恩·哈珀主持。
Today, we will hear
今天，我们将审理
"The Case of Who's to Blame for the Mystery Stain."
“谁该为神秘污渍负责的案件”。
Before we proceed, will the two parties
在我们继续之前，请双方当事人
please approach the bench with their court fees?
携带他们的法庭费用到法官席前。
[all] Ooh.
哦。
Judges, does this please the court?
法官们，这符合法庭要求吗？
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
Very pleased.
非常满意。
It's good to be the judge.
当法官真好。
Okay, I gotta ask.
好吧，我得问一下。
Is this court thing happening?
这场法庭戏是在进行中吗？
Is it not happening?
还是没在进行？
Right, sorry.
对，抱歉。
Let's begin. [sighs]
我们开始吧。[叹气]
Molly, please tell the court in your own words what happened.
莫莉，请用自己的话告诉法庭发生了什么。
Well, I loaned Mae this shirt
嗯，我把这件衬衫借给了梅，
and it came back with this stain.
结果还回来时上面有了这个污渍。
I've heard enough.
我已经听够了。
Molly, I sentence you to go out with me.
Molly，我判你和我出去约会。
Mae, what's your side of the story?
Mae，你那边的情况是怎样的？
Well, Molly loaned me the shirt, I wore it on Wednesday,
嗯，Molly借给我这件衬衫，我周三穿了它，
and when I gave it back, it didn't have a stain on it.
当我归还时，上面并没有污渍。
I've heard enough.
我已经听够了。
Mae, I sentence you to go out with me.
Mae，我判你和我出去约会。
Wait, Wednesday?
等等，周三？
Wasn't that the day that we did each other's nails?
那天不是我们互相做指甲的日子吗？
Yeah, but we didn't get any on the shirt.
是的，但我们没有弄到衬衫上。
We'll be the judges of that.
我们来做评判。
Let's see your nails.
让我们看看你的指甲。
And the shirt.
还有衬衫。
[gasping]
（倒抽气声）
Whoops. Guess I'm guilty.
哎呀，看来我有罪了。
The judges will now deliberate.
法官们现在要商议了。
Have you guys tried the mini hot dogs?
你们试过迷你热狗吗？
The fritter is so--
那个炸饼真是——
[all whispering excitedly]
（所有人都兴奋地低声讨论）
Are we getting a verdict?
我们是不是要宣判了？
Are we not getting a verdict?
我们是不是得不到判决了？
[all] Guilty!
全体：有罪！
Mae B. Valentine, the court sentences you
梅·B·瓦伦丁，法庭判决你
to apologize to Molly.
向莫莉道歉。
And replace her shirt.
并赔偿她的衬衫。
And go out with me.
还要和我出去约会。
Or get Molly to go out with me.
或者让莫莉和我出去约会。
Judge Dicky ain't picky.
法官迪基不挑剔。
Case closed. Argument settled.
案件结束。争论解决。
Let's eat.
我们吃吧。
- Mmm. - Oh.
- Oh, yeah. - Mmm.
Too bad we don't have any more cases.
I could really use a milkshake to wash down this fritter.
- More cases.
I wonder...
Anyone else have a case they'd like for us to settle?
Looks like justice is about to be served.
In my mouth.
[upbeat music]
I don't know what tastes better.
我不知道哪个味道更好。
"The Case of the Spitball Bandit"
“吐口水球大盗案”
or "The Case of the Lunch Line Cutter."
还是“午餐排队插队者案”。
Two great cases that taste great together.
两个很棒的案件，搭配起来味道也很好。
Oh.
哦。
Whoa, Mack's at it again.
哇，麦克的恶作剧又来了。
[whoopee cushion blows air]
（气垫爆破声）
[laughter]
（笑声）
That wasn't me!
那不是我！
I think I just sat on a whoopee cushion.
我想我刚刚坐到了一个气垫上。
[laughter]
笑声
Where does he keep coming up with these pranks?
他这些恶作剧都是从哪儿想出来的？
Forget the pranks.
别提恶作剧了。
Where does he keep coming up
他这些
with those delicious cinnamon rolls?
美味的肉桂卷又是从哪儿弄来的？
Oh! Mm. [stomach gurgles]
哦！嗯。[肚子咕噜声]
Oh, maybe Mom was right.
哦，也许妈妈是对的。
Maybe we should give up the Quad Court
也许我们应该放弃Quad Court
and start eating healthy.
开始吃健康点。
Just do what I do: eat through the pain.
就像我做的那样：忍痛吃下去。
The pain is just your stomach saying, "I want more."
疼痛只是你的胃在说，“我还要更多。”
[stomach growls]
[肚子咕噜声]
Oh.
哦。
See? That guy gets it.
看？那家伙明白了。
Guys, we've got a problem.
伙计们，我们有个问题。
We don't have any more cases.
我们没有更多的案件了。
This is the last of our junk food.
这是我们最后一点垃圾食品。
That's not a problem. We'll just get another case.
那不是问题。我们再弄一箱就行了。
I mean, kids are always fighting with each other. Yeah.
我是说，孩子们总是互相打架。是吧。
[laughter]
[笑声]
Doesn't look like it.
看起来不像。
Everyone is getting along.
大家相处得很好。
Do you think it's all because of Quad Court?
你认为这都是因为Quad Court吗？
Hey, guys. Everyone's getting along.
嘿，伙计们。大家相处得很好。
And it's all because of Quad Court.
而这都是因为Quad Court。
[upbeat music]
Ugh.
呃。
Ooh, carrots, huh?
哦，胡萝卜，是吗？
Nice.
不错。
You know, I am so proud of you and your dad
你知道吗，我为你和你爸爸终于吃对了感到非常骄傲。
for finally eating right.
为了终于开始正确饮食。
You know what?
你知道吗？
Wheat grass shots for everybody.
给每个人都来点小麦草汁。
[all] Yay!
耶！
[all groaning]
哎呀！
Delivery for Tom Harper.
给汤姆·哈珀的快递。
Looks like a whole lot of candy golf balls.
看起来像是一大堆糖果高尔夫球。
Shh!
嘘！
Just...play it cool.
就...保持冷静。
Oh, gotcha.
哦，明白了。
Don't worry, I do community theater.
别担心，我参加社区剧团的。
Hello, store owner.
你好，店主。
Here is your delivery of 100% real golf balls.
这是您订购的100%真高尔夫球。
Candy golf balls, you say?
你说的是糖果高尔夫球？
Why, no they're not.
哦，不，它们不是。
[fake laughs]
[假笑]
Nailed it.
完美搞定。
Here you go.
给您。
Thank you, thank you.
谢谢，谢谢。
Now...I'll have my own candy bowl.
现在...我会有自己的糖果碗了。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
Hidden in plain sight.
隐藏在众目睽睽之下。
Mm. Mm.
嗯。嗯。
You, sir, are a genius.
先生，你真是个天才。
Well, drink up.
好了，喝吧。
[chuckles]
（轻笑）
Good job. Way to get healthy, kids.
干得好。孩子们，这样才健康。
Ugh, this is what it's come to?
唉，这就到了这种地步吗？
Drinking grass?
喝草？
And drinking it again.
还要再喝一次。
I made your dad's extra wheat-y and grassy.
我把你爸的那份做得很麦香浓郁，草味十足。
[retches]
[作呕]
This has to stop.
这必须停止。
Quad Court needs more cases, fast.
四合院法庭需要更多案件，快点。
You know, just because everyone's getting along now
你知道，现在大家相处融洽
doesn't mean they'll always get along.
并不意味着他们会一直这样。
What if someone stirred up a little trouble?
如果有人挑起一点麻烦呢？
So you're suggesting we start fights
所以你建议我们挑起争斗
just to get more court cases?
只是为了增加法庭案件？
- That is unethical. - Immoral.
- 那是不道德的。 - 不道德。
And just plain wrong.
而且完全不对。
Hey, guys.
嘿，伙计们。
Why are you guys looking at me like that?
你们为什么那样看着我？
Okay.
好吧。
[all shuddering]
（所有人颤抖）
[all] I'm in.
（所有人）我加入。
Looks like someone needs to go to Quad Court.
看来有人需要去四方法庭。
And I know just how we're going to get him there.
而且我知道我们怎么让他去那里。
Mom!
妈妈！
Oh, no. I spit backwards.
哦，不。我向后吐。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
Okay, here comes Goldberg.
好的，Goldberg来了。
Operation "Fake Mack Attack So We Can Get Our Snacks Back"
“假Mack攻击以夺回我们的零食”行动
is a go.
开始。
Goldberg. My man, what's up?
Goldberg，哥们，怎么样？
Well, I lost my retainer in the bathroom after lunch,
嗯，午饭后我在洗手间丢了我的保持器，
so I called my mother,
所以我给我妈妈打了电话，
but then I dropped my phone in the toilet, and--
但后来我把手机掉进了马桶，然后——
Yeah, yeah, great talk.
是啊，是啊，聊得不错。
Can I borrow your history book?
我能借你的历史书吗？
It's in your locker. Let's go.
它在你的储物柜里。我们走吧。
Oh, hey, guys.
哦，嘿，伙计们。
Look who I found.
看看我找到了谁。
Why me?
为什么是我？
Having a disagreement?
有分歧吗？
Can't decide who's right or wrong?
决定不了谁对谁错吗？
Let the Quad Court decide.
让四方法庭来决定。
For a nom-nom-nominal fee.
象征性收费。
What is going on here?
这里发生了什么？
Mack.
麦克。
It wasn't me.
不是我。
That's it.
就是这样。
First, my tortoise.
首先，我的乌龟。
Then the whoopee cushion.
然后是放屁垫。
Now there are balls in the halls.
现在大厅里到处是球。
You are suspended.
你被停学了。
My office, now.
现在来我办公室。
- Wait, stop. It wasn't Mack.
等等，停下。不是Mack。
Oh, really? Then who was it, hmm?
哦，真的吗？那会是谁呢，嗯？
It was us.
是我们。
Look, kids, I appreciate you trying to stick up for your friend.
听着，孩子们，我理解你们想为朋友辩护的心情。
But all of the evidence points to Mack,
但所有的证据都指向Mack，
and that evidence says he's guilty.
那些证据表明他有罪。
Case closed.
案子结了。
Wait--
等等——
- Oh. - Here.
哦。
I won't be able to enjoy this where I'm going.
我去了那里就享受不了这个了。
I'm not going to be able to enjoy this either.
我也无法享受这个了。
- Yeah. - I agree.
是啊。
- So let's eat it sadly. - Yeah.
我同意。
[upbeat music]
Doesn't this feel great, Tom?
这感觉不是很棒吗，汤姆？
Don't you just feel... alive?
你不觉得...活着真好吗？
I feel... excruciatingly alive!
我感觉...活着真是太痛苦了！
[panting]
Oh, look, there's someone at the counter.
哦，看，柜台那边有人。
I'll be right back, okay?
我马上回来，好吗？
Okay. Whoo-hoo!
好的。哇呼！
Whoo-hoo!
哇呼！
[chuckles]
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Where are my sweet golf balls?
我的甜甜高尔夫球呢？
My sweet, sweet, candy golf balls.
我那甜甜的糖果高尔夫球。
Where's the sugar?
糖呢？
Where's the sweet?
甜味呢？
It's not there.
不在那儿。
[upbeat music]
[轻快的音乐]
We know how upset you are about Shelly,
我们知道你对Shelly感到多么难过，
and we think we have just the thing to cheer her up.
而且我们认为我们有一样东西可以让她开心起来。
Well, I hope this works, kids.
嗯，我希望这能奏效，孩子们。
Now where is this gentleman crawler you've found for Shelly?
那么，你们为Shelly找到的这个绅士爬行者在哪里？
Right here.
就在这儿。
That's a dog in a turtle costume.
那是一只穿着乌龟服装的狗。
What?
什么？
All right, Principal Tarian.
好吧，Tarian校长。
You caught us.
你抓到我们了。
We thought we could fool you,
我们以为能骗过你，
but you're obviously a man who can recognize the truth.
但你显然是一个能识别真相的人。
The whole truth and nothing but the truth.
全部的真相，没有半点虚假。
Which is why we hope you'll give us the chance
正因为如此，我们希望您能给我们一个机会
to show you the truth in...
向您展示真相在...
[all] The Quad Court!
[所有] 四方庭院！
Where we will prove we set up Mack.
在那里我们将证明我们陷害了Mack。
Kids, I'm sorry, but Mack is clearly guilty.
孩子们，我很抱歉，但Mack显然是有罪的。
You only think that because you haven't heard all the evidence.
您这么认为只是因为您还没有听到所有的证据。
Mack A. Damia, did you or did you not
Mack A. Damia，你有没有把那些高尔夫球放进Goldberg的储物柜？
put those golf balls in Goldberg's locker?
我没有！
I did not!
案件结束。
Case closed.
Mack，你可以自由离开了。
Mack, you're free to go.
Mack，你可以走了。
What? No, he's not.
什么？不，他不可以。
You haven't proven anything.
你什么都没证明。
But we're about to.
但我们即将证明。
We call our first witness,
我们传唤我们的第一个证人，
the Harper Quads.
Harper四胞胎。
[all] That's us.
就是我们。
Now, did we or did we not
那么，我们有没有
put those golf balls in Goldberg's locker?
把那些高尔夫球放进Goldberg的储物柜？
- Yes. - We did.
是的。我们放了。
Totally.
完全正确。
There you have it. The Quads are guilty.
这就是了。四胞胎有罪。
Case closed.
案子结了。
Mack A. Damian, you're free to go.
麦卡·达米安，你可以走了。
Now get out of here, you little nut.
现在离开这里，小家伙。
Ah, not so fast.
啊，没那么快。
You still haven't proven anything.
你还没有证明任何事情。
But these will.
但这些可以。
We took these from our dad's store, which proves we did it.
我们从爸爸的店里拿的，这证明是我们干的。
Those could have come from anywhere.
那些可能来自任何地方。
Look, I'm sorry, kids, but I don't see any evidence
听着，孩子们，我很抱歉，但我没有看到任何证据
that connects you to these particular golf balls.
能证明你们与这些特定的高尔夫球有关。
- Hey, kids.
- 嘿，孩子们。
Hey, Mack.
嘿，Mack。
Principal Tarian.
Tarian校长。
Don't mind me, I'm just looking for some particular golf balls.
别介意我，我只是在找一些特定的高尔夫球。
And these appear to be them.
而这些看起来就是它们。
See? They really are his.
看？它们真的是他的。
If they weren't his, would he lick them?
如果它们不是他的，他会舔它们吗？
- Of course he would because they're not really golf balls.
- 当然他会，因为它们其实不是高尔夫球。
They're candy.
它们是糖果。
[gasping]
[倒吸一口气]
It was Mack.
是Mack。
Case closed.
案子结了。
Mack, you're in a lot of trouble.
Mack，你麻烦大了。
No.
不。
Since the golf balls used in the crime
既然用于犯罪的这些高尔夫球
are clearly our dad's,
显然是我们爸爸的，
it proves Mack didn't do it.
那就证明Mack没有做这件事。
And we did.
而我们做了。
Well, I guess you're off the hook.
嗯，我想你没事了。
[all] Yes!
是的！
But you kids are in big trouble.
但你们这些孩子有大麻烦了。
[all] Oh.
哦。
I'll see you in my office first thing in the morning.
明天一早到我办公室来。
They'll be there, Principal Tarian.
他们会去的，Tarian校长。
I'm sorry, Mack.
对不起，Mack。
This is all because we couldn't give up eating junk food.
这都是因为我们戒不掉吃垃圾食品。
And our need for sweets made us do some not-so-sweet things.
我们对甜食的渴望让我们做了一些不太好的事。
Tell me about it.
说来话长。
Ever since my mom started making those cinnamon rolls,
自从我妈开始做那些肉桂卷以来，
I've been so sugared up I just haven't been myself.
我糖分摄入过多，已经变得不像我自己了。
Neither have we.
我们也是。
So, from now on, no sweets.
所以，从现在开始，不再吃甜食。
Well, seeing as this is where "no sweets" got us,
好吧，既然‘不吃甜食’让我们走到了这一步，
maybe we should aim for less sweets.
也许我们应该减少甜食的摄入。
- Yeah. - Yeah, that sounds good.
是的。
- I'm sorry to interrupt, but have you seen Shelly? I can't find her anywhere.
是的，听起来不错。
[upbeat music]
对不起打断一下，你们看到Shelly了吗？我到处都找不到她。
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling]
♪ [口哨声] ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪